Our database will contain weather forecast entries. Out data model will use
two tables. One table will be used to contain information about the location,
while the other will contain the forecast data keyed the locations.
These will ultimately be tied back to our view through the contract, and
the content provider. We can use an inner join, pull the complete data for
each forecast today. Including all information about the location. This,
is a big contract. Note that we store the location id, which will be a foreign
key from the location table in COLUMN_LOC_KEY. Note that the units aren't stored
in the database. We expect all weather entries to be stored in metric units, and
converted when needed by the UI, into imperial units. Since the column names
don't actually contain data types, it's useful to annotate that in
the variable names and/or the comments to make our contract more explicit.